A Guide to the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Administration, Records, 1997-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Assigned State Agencies, 2001-2005., Extent: 70 folders. (Box 18-26)
  - Human Resource Management, Dept. of--Workplace Harassment, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights, Council on, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, Dept. for, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Multiple Agency Material, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Support Services, Governor's Office of, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Virginia War Memorial Foundation, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Series VII. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation: Office of the Secretary, 2001-2005., Extent: 45 folders. (Box 27-30)
  Composed of correspondence and memos, as well as additional supporting documentation such as reports, proposals, brochures, and presentation material. The folders are arranged alphabetically according to the Secretariat under which the agency falls. Each Secretariat's office usually has its own folder, and sometimes several additional folders devoted to agencies under its heading. Notable files include those under the heading of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, which contain notifications of appointments to various boards and agency positions. Also found in these files are descriptive profiles of individual boards that answer to the Secretary of the Commonwealth, such as the Human Rights Council, the Design-Build-Construction Management Review Board, the Virginia Public Buildings Review Board, the Purchases and Supply Procurement Appeals Board, and the Capitol Square Preservation Council. Several files found under the heading of the Secretary of Education, Library of Virginia, document problems encountered by the library in terms of climate control and the protection of its collections. Another notable file can be found under the heading of the Secretary of Public Safety, Department of Corrections, Staunton Correctional Center. It contains information on the future adaptive re-use of the center, once known as Western State Hospital.
  - Commerce and Trade, Sec. of, 2002-2004 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Sec. of--Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Commerce and Trade, Sec. of--One Virginia-One Future, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Education, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Education, Sec. of--Community College System, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Education, Sec. of--Community College System: Tidewater Community College, Suffolk, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Education, Sec. of--Higher Education Summit, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Education, Sec. of--Library of Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Education, Sec. of--Library of Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Education, Sec. of--Library of Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Education, Sec. of--Science Museum of Virginia, 2002-2004 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Education, Sec. of--Superintendent of Education, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Education, Sec. of--University of Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Education, Sec. of--Virginia Commonwealth University, 2002-2004 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Education, Sec. of--Virginia Commonwealth University: Virginia Executive Institute, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Education, Sec. of--Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Education, Sec. of--Virginia Tech, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Finance, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Finance, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Finance, Sec. of--Accounts, Dept. of, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Finance, Sec. of--Accounts, Dept. of: Office of the Comptroller 2004-2005 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Finance, Sec. of--Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Finance, Sec. of, Treasury, Dept. of, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Health and Human Resources, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Health and Human Resources, Sec. of--Health, Dept. of, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Natural Resources, Sec. of--Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of--Corrections, Dept. of, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Public Safety, Sec. of--Corrections, Dept. of: Staunton Correctional Center, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Technology, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Technology, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Technology, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Technology, Sec. of, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Technology, Sec. of--Information Technology, Dept. of, 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Technology, Sec. of--Information Technology, Dept. of: Cabinet Technology Team, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Technology, Sec. of--Information Technology, Dept. of: IT Asset Information Certification, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Technology, Sec. of--IT Data Collection: "Due Dilligence," 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Technology, Sec. of--IT Data Collection: It Strategic Planning Certification, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Technology, Sec. of--Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Technology, Sec. of--Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Transportation, Sec. of, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Transportation, Sec. of--Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Series VIII. Environmental Impact Studies, 2002-2005., Extent: 66 folders. (Box 30-38)
  Contains environmental impact reports and statements created by state agencies before beginning construction projects. Section 10.1-1188 of the Code of Virginia requires that state agencies, institutions or branches of government proposing to undertake a "major state project" must prepare an environmental impact report. A "major state project" is defined as the construction of a facility costing $100,000 or more, or the acquisition of land for which construction is contemplated. The Governor's approval of the report is required before any funds are expended. The approval process was delegated to the Secretary of Administration by Executive Order 31 (94).
  The report packets include the memorandum of approval, approval with stipulations, or disapproval, several pages of comments made by the Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ), and other various memos and correspondence from specific departments that discuss the project and any possible ill affects it could have on the environment. The comments made by the DEQ take into account natural heritage and wildlife resources, air quality, waste management, historic and archeological resources, recreation, pollution, transportation and traffic, use of pesticides and herbicides, and energy conservation. Other topics addressed by the DEQ include erosion and sediment control, asbestos and lead paint problems, and any affect the project might have on the public water supply. Other agencies such as local governments, the Department of Historic Resources, the Department of Conservation and Recreation, the Department of Transportation, and regional planning district commissions were also consulted and asked to comment on any potential problems. The reports range from small renovations and additions, to large-scale construction efforts. Many of the projects took place on college campuses, at correctional facilities, and in marine areas. Several of the reports document the projects undertaken at the Jamestown Settlement in preparation for the 400th anniversary celebration in 2007. The environmental impact reports are filed by the date of the final approval or disapproval memo. Within each folder individual reports are filed in reverse chronological order.
  - Environmental Impact Report Chart, 2002-2004 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 February (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 March (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 April (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 May (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 May (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 June (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 July (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 August (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 August (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 September (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 October (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 November (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 November (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2002 December (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 January (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 February (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 March (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 April (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 May (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 May (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 June (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 July (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 August (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 September (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 October (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 November (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 November (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2003 December (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 January (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 February (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 March (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 March (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 April (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 April (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 May (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 June (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 July (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 July (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 August (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 September (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 October (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 November (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2004 December (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 January (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 February (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 March (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 March (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 April (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 April (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 May (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 May (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 June (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 June (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 July (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 July (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 July (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 July (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 August (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 September (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 September (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 October (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 October (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 November (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 December (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Reports and Statements, 2005 December (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Series IX. Freedom of Information Act Requests, 2002-2005., Extent: 4 folders. (Box 38)
  Consists of Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) requests and supporting documentation. Legislation regarding FOIA can be found in section 2.2-3700 of the Code of Virginia. It ensures citizens ready access to public records created and/or maintained by a public body. The first folder of this series contains information requests, several of which were denied because Virginia FOIA explicitly states that the Commonwealth is not required to furnish government documents to those who reside outside of the state. Other requests were denied on the grounds that the documentation in question did not exist. The remaining three folders contain correspondence, gaming permit applications, and lease information related to one request involving charitable gaming issues in the Hampton Roads area.
  - Freedom of Information Act Requests, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Freedom of Information Act Requests--Vaccarelli, Mike Jr.: Charitable Gaming, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Freedom of Information Act Requests--Vaccarelli, Mike Jr.: Charitable Gaming, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Freedom of Information Act Requests--Vaccarelli, Mike Jr.: Charitable Gaming, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Series X. Intellectual Property Rights, 2002-2005., Extent: 3 folders. (Box 39)
  Contains disclosures, correspondence and other supporting documentation for reporting all inventions in accordance with Virginia's Intellectual Properties Policy set forth by Executive Memorandum 4-95. This policy states that any employee of an executive branch agency who invents a potentially marketable or commercially valuable process, device, technique, or method during working hours, within the scope of employment, or when using state-owned or controlled facilities is required to disclose that information. The disclosure forms contain detailed descriptions of the inventions which include among others, an apparatus to support and store truck-mounted calcium chloride spreaders, a database for managing Freedom of Information Act requests, and a tracheotomy expectorant shield.
  - Intellectual Property Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Intellectual Property Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Intellectual Property Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Series XI. Legislative Files, 2002-2006., Extent: 145 folders. (Box 39-56)
  Contains enrolled bill reviews, legislative action summaries, legislative proposals and other miscellaneous legislation-related documents which explain in detail various bills brought before and voted upon by both the Senate and the House of Delegates. The Secretary of Administration was tapped by the Governor to respond to all General Assembly activity involving the agencies assigned to her office. Decisions were reached with the aid of agency heads with working knowledge of how legislation might affect the agency's ability to operate. The legislative files contain information on a number of subjects, the most prevalent being health care reform, voting, and campaign finance. Each enrolled bill review contains a summary of the bill and the number votes on passage achieved by the House and Senate. The reviews also include notations as to whether the Governor should sign, ask to amend, or to veto the bill. The legislative action summaries usually include whether the Secretary supported the bill, supported it with amendment, opposed the bill, or took no position on it. Most of the summaries contain comments and reasons for support or opposition. The legislative proposals are packets provided by individual agencies under the Secretary of Administration. Each proposal packet usually includes a statement of need for legislation within which ideas and suggestions for agency-specific legislation are documented. Also included in the legislative files are fiscal impact statements that detail the monetary affect any legislation might have on certain agencies, as well as reviews of carry-over legislation from the previous session.
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 26-235, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 238-507, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 536-721, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 729-1078, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 1082-1350, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 19-53, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 158-328, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 330-689, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 9-92, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 93-171, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 172-309, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 316-383, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 383-480, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 482-556, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 557-619, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 624-714, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 729-797, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 818-906, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 912-1014, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1015-1169, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1174-1326, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1327-1359, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Resolutions and Joint Resolutions, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1-99, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 100-175, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 177-264, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 269-401, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 403-496, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 520-689, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Reviews of Carry-over Legislation, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 1375-1590, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 1625-1774, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 1788-2062, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 2063-2343, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 2356-2656, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--House Bills 2666-2836, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 718-981, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 1012-1132, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 1161-1354, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Impact Statements--House Bills 1375-1917, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Fiscal Impact Statements--House Bills 1946-2836, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Fiscal Impact Statements--Senate Bills, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1375-1588, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1589-1683, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1692-1818, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1847-1967, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1968-2096, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2098-2192, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2194-2362, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2375-2573, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2619-2728, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 2619-2728, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Resolutions and Joint Resolutions, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 702-795, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 796-983, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1006-1132, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1150-1289, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--Senate Bills 1275-1354, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Budget Proposals for 2004-2006 Biennium, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Decision Package Narrative Justification--Compensation Board, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Decision Package Narrative Justification--Elections, State Board of, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Decision Package Narrative Justification--General Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Decision Package Narrative Justification--Human Rights, Council on, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Decision Package Narrative Justification--Veterans Services, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Decision Package Narrative Justification--Virginia War Memorial Foundation, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 1-150, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 151-350, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 351-550, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 551-850, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 851-1150, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Enrolled Bill Reviews--Senate Bills 1151-1450, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Fiscal Impact Statements--House Bills, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Impact Statements--Senate Bills, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Legislation Implementation Updates, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Legislation Implementation Updates, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Legislation Implementation Updates, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 1-150, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 151-250, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 251-400, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 401-500, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 501-650, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 651-750, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 751-850, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 851-950, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Action Summaries--House Bills 951-1000, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 5)